{
  "id": "flashcard-mixed-3",
  "title": "Kanji 3",
  "description": "Luyện tập từ vựng: Thời gian, Số đếm & Con người.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "私",
      "answer": "tôi",
      "speak": "watashi"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "一人",
      "answer": "một người",
      "speak": "hitori"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "二人",
      "answer": "hai người",
      "speak": "futari"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "三人",
      "answer": "ba người",
      "speak": "sannin"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "才",
      "answer": "tuổi",
      "speak": "sai"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "学びます",
      "answer": "học",
      "speak": "manabimasu"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "学生",
      "answer": "học sinh, sinh viên",
      "speak": "gakusei"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "学校",
      "answer": "trường học",
      "speak": "gakkou"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "日本",
      "answer": "Nhật Bản",
      "speak": "nihon"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "本",
      "answer": "sách",
      "speak": "hon"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "日本語",
      "answer": "tiếng Nhật",
      "speak": "nihongo"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "日本語学校",
      "answer": "trường tiếng Nhật",
      "speak": "nihongogakkou"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "一月",
      "answer": "tháng 1",
      "speak": "ichigatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "木",
      "answer": "cây",
      "speak": "ki"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "お金",
      "answer": "tiền",
      "speak": "okane"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "何",
      "answer": "cái gì",
      "speak": "nani"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "年",
      "answer": "năm",
      "speak": "toshi"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "九時",
      "answer": "9 giờ",
      "speak": "kuji"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "四時",
      "answer": "4 giờ",
      "speak": "yoji"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "時間",
      "answer": "thời gian",
      "speak": "jikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "人間",
      "answer": "con người",
      "speak": "ningen"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "分かります",
      "answer": "hiểu",
      "speak": "wakarimasu"
    },
    
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "五月",
      "answer": "tháng 5",
      "speak": "gogatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "六人",
      "answer": "6 người",
      "speak": "rokunin"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "七日",
      "answer": "mùng 7, 7 ngày",
      "speak": "nanoka"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "八月",
      "answer": "tháng 8",
      "speak": "hachigatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "九月",
      "answer": "tháng 9",
      "speak": "kugatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "十月",
      "answer": "tháng 10",
      "speak": "juugatsu"
    }
  ]
}